Peyton Rous Papers 1909-1970 Mss.B.R77
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, ca.1917-1970; 47.0 Linear feet (Box 1-85)
  - Rous, Peyton
    - The Virus Tumors, 1938; Rous, Peyton
    - Viruses and Tumors, Rous, Peyton
    - Rous, F P: Viruses in Relation to Malignancy
    - Vitamins (with Photos), Rous, Peyton
    - What the Viruses tell concerning cancer causation, Rous, Peyton
    - What Viruses could do, Rous, Peyton
    - What we know Pap virus, Rous, Peyton
    - What we know about the masked virus, Rous, Peyton
    - Wild Rabbit cancers (Photos), Rous, Peyton
    - Wild Rabbit Cancers and Paps (Photos), Rous, Peyton
    - Withering Lecture, Rous, Peyton
    - Work of Rous, F. S. Jones and O. S. Robertson to Jan. 3, 1915, Rous, Peyton
    - Work of the Laboratory for Cancer Research, 1909-1912; Rous, Peyton
    - Wrong Direction for Weiss, Rous, Peyton
  - Rous, Helen Woods
  - Rous, Marion
    - Zabrieskie, Edwin G
    - Jordan, Henry H
  - Rous, Marion Charles
  - Rous, Marion Charles. Clinic Expenses, 1963
  - Rous, Simonne
  - Rous, William J
  - Rouse, Charles H
  - Rouse, Emma M
  - Rous-Turner Test (Photographs)
  - Roussy, Gustave
  - Routh, Dunlop
  - Routh, James E
  - Rowe, Max
    - Lawrence, John H
  - Rowntree, L G
  - Royal Academy of Sciences of Denmark
    - Knudsen, Martin
  - Royal Prince Alfred Hospital
    - Schlink, Herbert H
  - Royal Society of London
    - Davies, John Griffith
    - Martin, D C
    - Salisbury, Sir Edward J
    - Hinshelwood, Sir Cyril
    - Seward, Sir Albert Charles
    - Colby, Mrs.
    - Craig, Eunice G
    - Cramer, W
    - Dakin, Susan D H
    - Cambridge, U. of Trinity College
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Harrison, Ross G
    - Heggie, S M
    - Heidelberger, Michael
    - Ing, H Raymond
    - Jacobs, W A
    - Kennaway, E L
    - Kubie, Lawrence S
    - Ledingham, J C G
    - Levene, P A
    - Malloch, Archibald
    - Mansbridge, Ronald
    - McEwen, Currier
    - Mirsky, Alfred E
    - Moore, J S
    - Norton, M D Herter
    - Robey, William H
    - Rous, Mrs. F
    - Sabin, Florence Rena
    - Shope, R E
    - Smith, G M
    - Spies, Tom D
    - Swift, Homer F
    - Topley, W W C
    - Van Slyke, Donald D
    - Woglom, W H
    - Wolbach, S B
    - Wormall, A
    - Yerkes, Robert M
  - Royal Society of Medicine, London
    - Martin, D C
    - Edwards, Geoffrey R
    - Adrian, Lord
    - Bronk, Detlev
    - Whitaker, Douglas
    - MacKenzie, Ian
  - Royal Society of Medicine Foundation
    - Hewitt, Richard T
    - Herge, J Curtis
    - Boyer, Francis
    - Lloyd, R McAllister
    - Porritt, Sir Arthur
    - Cawthorne, Sir Terence
    - Thomson, Robert N
  - Rubin, Harry
    - Vogt, Peter K
  - Rudnick, Dorothea
  - Ruffilli, D
  - Rusch, H P
  - Rusk, Howard A
  - Russ, Henry C
  - Russell, Frederick F
  - Russell, Paul F
  - Russell, Walter C
  - Russell, William O
  - Rutherford, Guy G
  - Ruthven, Alexander G
  - Rutter, Arthur, Sons & Co.
  - Ryan, Jerry D
  - Rydenfelt, Sven
  - Ryder, Henry W
  - S.M.S. Medical College
  - Sabin, Albert B
  - In re Sabin, Florence Rena
    - Robinton, Elizabeth D
  - Sachs, Emanie N
  - Sachs, Ernest
  - Sachs, Julius
  - Sachs, Leo
    - Weizmann Institute of Science
    - Berenblum, I
  - Sachs, Paul
  - Sacks, Jerome H
  - Sage, Harold H
  - Sager, Alan
  - Sahyoun, Philip F
  - St. John - Brooks, Ralph
    - Gregg, Alan
  - St. Lawrence University
  - Sakalosky, George P
  - Salaman, M H
  - Salen, Elvin E
  - Salomon, Jean Claude
  - Salter, William T
  - Salzburg, Peter
  - Sanchez, Hector
  - Sanders, Murray
  - Sandoz Chemical Works, Inc.
  - Sands, John L
  - Sanford, A H
  - Sangiorgio, Frank E
    - Prior, Moody E
    - Mead, Albert R
  - Santesson, L
  - Santini, G
  - Sarles, Meritt P
  - Saunders, W.B., Company
  - Sawin, Paul B
  - Satterlee, Henry S
  - Sawyer, Wilbur A
  - Saxe, Edward L
  - Saxton, Eugene F
  - Saxton, William
    - Maxwell, William
  - Say, H A
  - Schaefer, Helen J
  - Schaffner, Sara H
  - Schanin, A P
  - Schatten, William E
  - Schenker, Ben W
  - Schinz, Hans R
  - Schlaepfer, Karl
  - Schlesinger, R Walter
  - Schloss, Oscar M
  - Schmeisser, Harry Christian
  - Schmidt, Louis
  - Schmitt, Kenneth
  - Schneider, Howard A
    - Institute for Biomedical Research
  - Schorer, Mark
  - Schottstaedt, W E R
  - Schram, Mildred W S
  - Schramm, W R
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Schrek, Robert
  - Schumacher, Paul
  - Schutz, F W
    - Henderson, James S
  - Schwartz, Nathan
  - Schwartz, Solomon
  - Science
    - Stahle, Nils K
    - Waldman, Seymour N
    - Olney, Mrs. Helen
    - Abelson, Philip H
    - Cattell, J McKeen
    - Atwood, Mildred A
    - Valentine, Willard L
  - Science Information Exchange
  - Science Service
  - Scott, C M
  - Scott, Mrs. David
  - Scott, Edwin M
  - Scott, W J M
  - Scott, Walker
    - Bryson, Edward W
    - McDowell, William J
    - Gay, Thomas B
    - Jones, T Catesby
    - Rous, Marion
  - Scribner's, Charles, Sons
    - Heuer, Kenneth
  - Seabrook, William
  - Seal, S H
  - Seale, John
  - Seaman, Arlene R
  - Searle, R M
  - Second International Congress for Microbiology
    - St.John-Brooks, R
  - Segal, Herman
  - Seitz, Frederick
  - Sellards, Watson
  - Sellei, Camillo
  - Selye, Hans
  - Semachko
  - Senn, A
    - Carrel, Alexis
  - Seventh International Cancer Congress
    - Scarff, Robert W
    - Whitaker, Douglas
    - Dorn, Harold F
    - Kidd, John G
    - Maisin, J H
    - Paterson, Ralston
    - Rogers, Stanfield
    - Whitaker, Douglas
  - Sewall, Henry
  - Shaffer, Philip A
  - Shapira, Pauline
  - Shattuck, Mrs. Mary
    - Watson, Robert F
  - Shaughnessy, Edward
  - Shaunag, A M
  - Shear, Murray J
  - Shearer, Marshall L., Jr.
  - Shedlovsky, Theodore
  - Sheehan, Donald
  - Sheldon, Huntington
  - Shellman, Arthur P
  - Shepard, Edward M
  - Sherman, William B
  - Shields, Warren
  - Shimkin, Michael B
  - Shingleton, William W
  - Shockley, William
  - Shope, Richard E
  - Shope, R. Photographs
  - Shotts, Emmett Booker
    - Gratzek, John B
  - Shotwell, W H
  - Shrigley, E W
  - Shriver, William P
  - Shryock, Richard Harrison
  - Shubik, Philippe
  - Shwartzman, Gregory
    - Hirst, George K
  - Sidamon-Eristoff, Anne
  - Siemonn, George
  - Sigelman, Saul
  - Sigma Xi
    - Reutner, R
    - Baitsell, George A
    - Burns, Edward L
    - Cartledge, J L
    - Clark, Paul F
    - Easton, J Clark
    - Eyster, William
    - Graves, K D
    - Lamont, William H F
    - Murray, John W
    - Nelson, Thurlow C
    - Pegram, George B
    - Reimann, Stanley P
    - Sheppard, Oden E
    - Stewart, Chester A
    - Tomlinson, Hazel M
    - Trout, Hugh H
    - Visscher, Maurice B
    - Vyssotsky, A N
    - Wangensteen, Owen H
    - Weber, Robert L
    - Baitsell, George A
  - Silberstein, Fritz
  - Sills, H D
  - Silversmith, Norman
    - White, Abraham
    - Markee, J E
    - Davison, Wilburt C
    - Anderson, Donald G
  - Simmons, D A
  - Simms, Henry S
  - Simons, P J
  - Simonson, Mrs. Louise O
    - Lab World
  - Simpson, A F
  - Simpson, Meriam E
  - Skopek, Henry A
  - Skoryna, Stanley C
  - Sladen, Frank J
  - Slaughter, George W
  - Slemons, J Morris
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer
    - Research, (22 Folders)
    - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr.
    - Bradley, Stanley E
    - Eagle, Harry
    - Cohen, Seymour S
    - Weaver, Warren
    - Lloyd, R McAllister
    - Dalldorf, Gilbert
    - Kilham, Lawrence
    - Bearn, Alexander G
    - Arnold, Richard T
    - Abramson, Ruth
    - Roeters, A
    - Berg, John
    - Hess, H Lawrence
    - Mecke, Bernhard L
    - Karnofsky, David A
    - Rhoads, Cornelius P
    - Denues, A R T
    - Mellors
    - Strong, Leonell C
    - Belmer, Barbara J
    - Breen, Ann
    - Gallagher, T F
    - Rienow, H W
    - Stewart, Fred
    - Stock, C Chester
    - Weaver, Warren
    - Mellors, Robert C
    - Rapport, M M
    - Korngold, L
    - Skipski, V
    - Graf, L
    - Friend, Charlotte
    - Toolan, Helene Wallace
    - Moore, Alice E
    - Laughlin, John S
    - Rowe, Max
    - Riley, Vernon
    - Sugiura, Kanematsu
    - Wynder, Ernest L
    - Wade, Leo
    - Bendich, Aaron
    - Philips, Frederick S
    - Tamm, Igor
    - Noyes, Wilbur F
    - Bale, William F
    - Cole, Warren H
    - Deitrick, John E
    - London, Irving M
    - Shope, Richard E
    - Stetson, Chandler A
    - Tatum, Edward L
    - Schmitt, Francis O
    - Karnofsky, David A
    - Lilienfeld, Abraham M
    - Hotchkiss, Rollin D
    - Janoff, Aaron
    - DuShane, Graham
    - Simpson, George Gaylord
  - Slye, Maud
  - Smadel, Joseph E
  - Smillie, E W
  - Smith, Alan De Forest
  - Smith, Carl H
  - Smith, Chard
  - Smith, David Eugene
  - Smith, Edric B
    - Wasserman, Felix
  - Smith, Edward B
  - Smith, Erwin F
  - Smith, Frederick
  - Smith, George A
  - Smith, George M
  - Smith, Gertrude C
  - Smith, Harrison
  - Smith, Homer W
  - Smith, Honor
  - Smith, John Henderson
  - Smith, J James
  - Smith, Kay Barlour
  - Smith, Kenneth M
  - Smith, Lionel
  - Smith, Lloyd H., Jr.
    - Gilbert, Marianne
  - Smith, Margaret H D
  - Smith, Mrs. Mary F
  - Smith, Nannette
  - Smith, Theobald
  - Smith, W Gordon
  - Smith, William E
    - Selikoff, Irving J
    - Lasker, Mrs. Albert D
    - Dessau, F I
    - Weaver, Harry M
    - Sammartino, Peter
    - Hellbaum, Arthur A
    - Towns, Mrs. Jane B
    - Kidd, John C
  - Smithburn, Kenneth C
  - Smithsonian Institution
  - Smolian, Steven J
  - Smolker, Mrs. Rosemary G
  - Snell, Katharine C
  - Snell, P Edson
  - Snover, Sarah J
  - Snyder, John C
  - Snyder, Martin
  - Snyder, Stuart S
  - Snyderman, Reuven K
    - Calne, R Y
    - Stansly, Philip G
  - Societe Anatomique pour L'Etude de Cancer
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine
    - Goldforb, A J
    - Stewart, Florence M
    - Andervont, H B
    - Mooser, Herrmann
    - Rogers, Stanfield
    - Gordon, Albert S
    - Greenwald, Isidor
    - MacNeal, Ward J
    - Myers, Victor C
    - Chambers, Robert
    - Jobling, James W
    - Smith, Theobald
    - Lewis, Paul
    - Cutler, Elliott C
    - Sherwin, Carl P
    - Van Slyke, Donald D
    - Allen, Edgar
    - Carlson, A J
    - Dochez, A R
    - Doisy, E A
    - Gesell, Robert
    - Kennedy, Norman F
    - Ivy, A C
    - Murlin, John R
    - Riddle, Oscar
    - Curtis, W C
    - Cushing, Harvey
    - Sondern, Frederic E
    - Dodds
    - Davis, N C
    - Lieb, Charles Christian
    - Watson, D Lindsay
    - Malloch, Archibald
    - Myers, Victor C
    - Stockard, C R
    - Wood, Francis C
    - Packchanian, A
    - Beckwith, T D
    - Benedict, Stanley R
    - Carlson, A J
    - Edwards, Dayton J
    - Luckhardt, Arno B
    - Lusk, Graham
    - Ophuts, W
    - Palmer, Walter W
    - Harris, W H
    - Hines, H M
    - Liddell, H S
    - Scott, F H
    - Shaffer, P A
    - Wu, Hsien
    - Wallace, George B
    - Cohn, A E
    - Oliver, Jean
    - Wyckoff, Ralph W G
    - McMaster
    - Hess, Alfred F
    - Karsner, Howard T
    - Marine, David
    - McMaster, Philip D
    - Pearl, Raymond
    - Reynolds, Frederick P
    - Shapley, Harlow
    - Sokoloff
    - Stockard, Charles R
    - TenBroeck, Carl
    - Williams, Linsly R
  - Society for Investigative Dermatology
    - Hambrick, George W., Jr.
    - Peck, S M
  - Society of American Bacteriologists
    - Rivers, Thomas M
    - Francis, Thomas, Jr.
    - Morton, Harry E
  - Society of Cellular Biology
    - Chambers, Robert
    - Richards, A N
  - Soller, Theodore
  - Soloway, Henry B
  - Sondern, Frederic E
  - Sonneborn, T M
  - Sorenson, Burt P
  - Soule, George Henry, Jr.
  - Southam, C M
  - Southern Society of Clinical Surgeons
    - Hennsessey, Russell A
    - Crisler, J A., Jr.
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Spain, Will Cook
  - Sparrow, Carroll Macy
  - Speert, Harold
  - Speiser, Paul
  - Spies, Tom D
  - Spinelli, Antonio
  - Spitz, Harry
  - Spoerl, Myrma
  - Springer, Georg F
  - Sprunt, Douglas H
  - Stacy, Leda June
  - Stahle, Nils K
  - Stains
    - Cornwall, Ralph T K
    - Abel, John J
    - Brown, E W
    - Clark, William Mansfield
    - Dawson, A B
    - Eastman Kodak
    - Hooper, Charles W
    - Howland, John
    - Hynson, Westcott & Dunning
    - Larimore, L D
    - Lewis, Margaret Reed
    - Mallory, F B
    - Orndorff, W R
    - Richards, A N
    - Walton, D C
    - Wolbach, S Burt
  - Stanfield, J Fisher
  - Stankovich, George
  - Stankovich, Simone
  - Stanley, Wendell M
  - Stanton, E MacD
  - Stanton, Mearl F
  - State Institute for Study of Malignant Diseases
    - Warner, Stanley G
  - Stearns, Guy Beckley
  - Stebbins, Frances F
    - Schmidt, Louis
  - Stecher, Robert M
    - Lipschutz, Alexander
    - Woodruff, A W
  - Stechert-Hafner, Inc.
  - Steckel, Mrs. Jessie E
  - Stecher, Robert M. Darwin-Bates Letters
  - Steele, J Murray
  - Steen, Carl
  - Stefani, Walter
  - Stein, Mrs. Madge T
  - Stein, Mrs. Marguerite T
  - Steiner, Paul E
  - Stenkvist, Bjorn
  - Stephen, G N
  - Stern, Gustav
  - Stern, H
  - Stevens, Alexander Raymond
    - Saltonstall, Jock
    - Deming, Clyde
  - Stevenson, Alan John
  - Stevenson, Gordon
  - Stevenson, Peter C
  - Stanley, W M
  - Stewart, Doris
  - Stewart, Florence M
    - Chase, Merrill W
    - Broadbent, Margaret
  - Stewart, Fred W
  - Stewart, George N
  - Stewart, Harold L
  - Stewart, Matthew J
  - Stewart, W
    - Kidd, John G
  - Stich, W
  - Stickler, Mrs. Fred
  - Stillman, Edgar
  - Stimpert, Fred D
  - Stirling, Arthur C
  - Stiteler, Rowland H
  - Stitt, Edward W., Jr.
  - Stocks and Securities
  - Stokes, William Royal
  - Stokowski, Leopold
  - Stoll, Norman R
  - Stone, Dewey D
  - Stoner, William H
  - Storey, Harold T
  - Straubenmuller Textile High School
  - Streeter, George L
  - Strom, Peer
  - Strong, Mrs. Katherine B
  - Strong, Leonell C
  - Strong, Richard P
  - Stroud, Agnes Blanding
  - Stuart-Harris, C H
  - Stunkard, Horace W
  - Sturgis, Cyrus C
  - Sturtevant, A H
  - Suarez H., E
  - Sugiura, Kanematsu
  - Sulzberger, Marion B
  - Suntzeff, Valentina
  - Suter, W E
  - Sutton, Joseph G
  - Svet-Moldavsky, George J
  - Svodoba, Jan
    - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr.
  - Swarthmore College
    - Blanshard, Mrs. Brand
    - Philips, Anne
    - Aydelotte, F
  - Swedish Cancer Society
  - Swedish Radio
    - Feldreich, Bengt
    - Handler, Joseph
  - Swets & Zeitlinger
  - Swift, Homer F
  - Swiller, Lewis H
  - Symeodidis, Alexander
  - Symposium - Functional Components of Carcinogenesis. Israel, 1959
    - Brainin
    - Barenblum, I
    - Danielson, Mrs. Phyllis A
    - Loewenstein, Martha
    - Mandelbaum, A
    - Weisgal, Meyer W
  - Syverton, Jerome T
    - Olitsky, Peter K
  - Szane, P
  - Szent-Gyorgyi, Albert
  - Szybalski, Waclaw
  - Taft, A E
  - Tal, Chloe
    - Goebel, Walther F
    - Karnofsky, David A
  - Talalay, Paul
  - Talbot, T R., Jr.
  - Taliaferro, W H
  - Tannenbaum, Albert
  - Tannenberg, Joseph
  - Tashiro, Shiro
  - Tatum, Edward L
  - Tausig, Helen B
  - Taylor, Alfred
  - Taylor, Davidson
  - Taylor, Harriett E
  - Tealdi, Aubrey
  - Technical Meetings information service
  - Techniques, Histological
    - Cutts, G Harry
    - Rivers, Thomas M
  - Tee-Van, Mrs. John
  - Tekverk, Joseph
  - Temin, Howard M
  - Temple, Harold L
  - TenBroeck, Carl
  - Ten Eyck, Mrs. Maude E
  - Tenney, W Chandler
  - Terhune, Sidney H
  - Terpilak, Michael S
    - Chant, Harry L
    - Dees, J M., Jr.
    - Snyder, Ralph E
  - Terry, Mrs. Arthur
  - Texas-West
    - Rushing, Joe B
    - Kyger, Murray
    - Fisher, Beeman
    - Nelson, Joe T
  - The, Guy De
  - Theiss, Madge
  - Theiss, Marguerite M
  - Thieriot, L C
  - Think
  - Third International Congress for Microbiology
    - Rivers, Thomas M
    - Sawyer, Wilbur A
  - Thjotta, Th
  - Thomas, Charles C
  - Thomas, Colin G., Jr.
  - Thomas, Henry M., Jr.
  - Thomas, Mrs. L
  - Thomas, Robert P
  - Thomas, Thornton W
  - Thomas, William S
  - Thompson, J H
  - Thompson & Morgan, Ltd.
  - Thorne, J O
    - Collocott, Thomas C
  - Thornton, Helen
  - Tileston, Wilder
  - Tilghman, R Carmichael
  - Tillett, William S
  - Time
  - Tissue Acidosis
    - Cannon, Walter B
    - Cole, Rufus
    - Davison, Wilburt C
    - Hill, A V
    - Howland, John
    - Robinson, Canby
    - Zinsser, Hans
  - Tjernberg, Bengt
  - Today's Health
    - Arnold, Harriet
    - Cooley, Donald G
    - Liston, James M
  - Todd, C
  - Toksvig, Signe
  - Toone, W M
  - Topley, W W C
  - Townsend, Frank M
  - Trask, L M D
  - Travel Bureau Inc.
  - Trawley Realty Corp.
  - Trenner, Idamae Gail
  - Treves, Norman
  - Trinklein, Frederick E
  - Troan, John
  - Trout, Hugh H
  - Trowbridge, Mason
  - Tsaltas, Theodore T
  - Tunis, Barbara
  - Turin, Accademia di Medicina
    - Anguissola, A Beretta
    - Mottura, Giacome
    - Waksman, Byron H
  - Turner, J W Cecil
    - Kotschnig, Walter M
  - Turner, Joseph C
  - Turner, Joseph R
  - Turner, Kenneth B
  - Turner, Mary E
    - Lawrie, Elizabeth
  - Turner, Ross
  - Turner, Thomas B
  - Turner, Victor R
  - Tyler, Charles R
  - Tyrrell, David
  - Tyson, Floyd T
  - Tyzzer, E E
  - Uhlenhuth, Eduard
    - Bronk, Detlev W
  - Ullman, S B
  - Unger, Lester J
  - Unio Internationalis Contra Cancrum
  - United States of America: Affidavit of Support
  - United Nations, Prize for
    - Rosenberry, S L
    - Warren, Shields
    - Sugiura, Kanematsu
    - Bronk, Detlev W
    - Cumming, C N Wentworth
    - Thant, U
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Bolling, Richard
    - Bloom, David
  - U.S. Customs
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor - Bureau of Immigration
  - U.S. Dept. of State
  - U.S. Food and Drug Administration
  - U.S. Surgeon General
  - U.S. War Department
    - Armstrong, George E
  - University of Cambridge. Trinity Hall
    - Fleming, W L S
    - Putnam, Albert D
  - University of Chicago Press
    - Narita, Georgie
  - University of Michigan.
    - French, A. James
  - University of N.C.
    - Brinkhous, K M
    - Sommer, Elizabeth
  - University of Penna.
    - Kline, David G
    - Ravdin, I S
  - University of Penna. Bicentennial Celebration
  - University of Pennsylvania Press
    - Westlake, Mrs. Neda
  - University of Rochester
    - Orbison, J. Lowell
    - Terry, Roger W
    - Whipple, George H
  - University of Sydney
    - Molloy, M
  - University of Texas
    - Russell, William O
    - Rivers, Thomas M
    - Trichter, Jerome
  - University of the South
    - Webb, John M
  - University of Toronto
    - Ham, Arthur
  - University of Zurich
    - Spoerri, T
    - Fanconi, Guido
    - Schinz, H R
  - Urey, Harold C
  - Urobilin
  - Uzelatz, Vladislav S
  - Van Allen, Chester Montague
  - Van Cleve, Mrs. Florence
  - Vann, Mrs. Eugene Ellis
  - Van Scott, Eugene J
  - Van Slogteren, E
  - Van Slyke, Donald D
    - Bond, V P
  - Van Wesep, H B
  - Veendorp, Liesbet
  - Veeraraghavan, P
  - Veith, Ilza
  - Vigneaud, Vincent Du
  - Vilas, Homer A
  - Visscher, Maurice B
  - Vittaz, Caroline
  - Voegtlin, Carl
  - Voet, R
    - Weaver, Warren
    - Weir, John M
  - Vogel, Adolph W
  - Vogt, Peter K
  - Von Berg, Hilda A
    - Sabin, Albert B
  - Von Der Osten, Anna
  - von Eckermann, Mrs. Ebba
  - Von Hofgaarden, Luther
  - Vx Tumor
    - Hodes, M E
    - Henderson, James S
    - Thatcher, Sandra
    - Bethune, John E
    - Matsuo, Yutaka
    - Roof, Betty
    - Necheles, H
    - Baden, Howard P
    - Krain, L Stirling
    - Burns, Kenneth F
    - Herter, Frederic P
    - Cole, Donald R
    - Minton, John Peter
    - Evans, Charles A
    - Gregorie, H B., Jr.
    - Huebner, Robert J
    - Ito, Yohei
    - Krell, Rita
    - Kinmonth, J B
    - Linke, Charles A
    - Mango, Giorgio
    - Noyes, Wilbur F
    - Palmer, Catherine Gardella
    - Rose, Lawrence
    - Scheinberg, Labe C
    - Atchison, Robert W
    - Bryant, Samuel, Jr.
  - Vytus, Peter
  - Wachtel, Mrs. H
  - Wadia, D N
    - Bronk, Detlev W
  - Wadsworth, Augustus B
  - Wahl, Jonathan
  - Waife, S O
  - Wakerlin, George Earle
  - Waksman, Selman, A
  - Walcott, F C
  - Walker, Bradford
  - Walker, George
  - Walker, W Bradford
  - Walker Prize
    - Connell, Mrs. V
    - Wolfenden, J H
    - Stone, P W
    - Williams, D F P
    - Conard White Star, Ltd.
    - Sparks, Sir T Ashley
    - Shipley, Mrs. R B
    - Cassels, Kennedy
    - Webb-Johnson, Alfred
    - Lett, Sir Hugh
    - Levene, Ann
    - Childs, S Winston, Jr.
    - Childs, Starling W
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Heggie, R W
    - MacNider, William
    - Sendroy, Julius, Jr.
    - Van Slyke, Donald D
    - Wolbach, Burt
    - Williams, Charles M
  - Wallace, George B
    - Bodo, Richard
  - Wallach, Gert M K
  - Wallerstein Laboratories
    - Gray, Philip P
  - Walters, Basil L
  - Wang, T K
  - Wangensteen, Owen H
  - Wansbrough-Jones, O H
  - Warburg, Bettina
  - Warburg, Otto
    - Wood, Francis C
  - Warburton, Gladys
  - Ward, Edward M., Jr.
  - Ward, Sylvanus D
  - Warfield, A W
  - Warfield, Louis M
  - Warren, Shields
  - Warren, Stafford L
  - Warthin, Aldred Scott
    - Malone, Dumas
    - Weller, Carl V
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Warthin, Mrs. Aldred Scott
  - Warthin, Nathaniel A
  - Warthin, Thomas A
  - Wasielenski, Th Von
  - Wasley, W L
  - Wasteneys, Hardolph
  - Waters, Nelson F
  - Watson, C J
    - Bailey, Percival
  - Watson, John H L
  - Watters, Patrick & Joseph
  - Watts, Donald Tappan
  - Watts, Mrs. Philip Bartley
  - Weaver, Harry M
    see: American Cancer Society, Inc.
  - Weaver, James
  - Weaver, Lela M
  - Weaver, Warren
  - Webb, Gerald B
  - Webb, L C
  - Weber, Robert L
  - Weber, S E
  - Webster, Douglas
  - Webster, Jerome P
  - Webster, Leslie T
  - Weed, Lewis H
  - Weiner, Milton
  - Wein Hing
  - Weinman, Elizabeth D
    - Voorhees
  - Weinman, Howard
  - Weinman, Mrs. Howard
  - Weisbroth, Steven H
  - Weisgal, Meyer W
  - Weiss, David W
    - Moe, Henry Allen
  - Weiss, Paul A
    - Barsky, James
  - Weiss, Soma
  - Weizmann Institute of Science
    - Brainin, Joseph
    - Simons, John
    - Weisgal, Meyer W
    - Katchalski, Ephraim
    - Passow, Isidore David
    - Weisgal, Meyer W
  - The Weizman Institute of Science: American Committee
  - Weizman Institute of Science. Rehovoth
    - Berenblum, I
    - Brainin, Joseph
    - Mandelbaum, A
    - Loewenstein, Martha
    - Weisgal, Meyer W
  - Welch, Margaret
  - Welch, William H
  - Welch Medical Library
    - Larkey, Sanford V
  - Weld, Julia T
  - Weller, Carl V
  - Wells, H Gideon
    - Weil, Richard
  - Wells, Warren
  - Welo, Lars A
  - Werkstrom, Orjan
  - Werner, R
    - Pearce, Richard M
    - Teuschlander
  - Wertheimer Tovias, Yvette
  - Wesson, Miley B
  - West, Daisy H
  - West, Davenport
  - West, Randolph
  - Westphal, Otto
  - Weyman Institute
    - Sachs, Leo
  - Wheeler, John M
  - Wheeler School
    - Klock, Edwin J
    - Atwood, E V
    - Hewitt, Thomas D
    - Smith, F C
    - McDonald, Anthony L
    - Boynton, A S
    - Gray, C Ernest
  - Wheelock, Frederick
  - Wheelock, John Hall
  - Whipple, Allen O
  - Whipple, George H
    - Brown, G O
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Queen, Frank B
    - Robscheit-Robbins, F S
    - Terry, Rogert
  - Whitaker, Douglas
    from Whitaker, Douglas to Roof, Betty Sams
  - White, Abraham
  - White, David O
  - White, Ethel Bowen (Mrs. Franklin W White)
  - White, Franklin W
  - White, Jack E
  - White, Philip R
  - Whiteside, Thomas
  - Whitlock, W Melvin
  - Whitney, Mrs. Eunice
  - Whitney, Frank
  - Whitney, William
  - Who's important in medicine?
  - Who Knows - and what
  - Who's who
  - Who's who among physicians and surgeons
  - Who's who in America
  - Who's who in New York
  - Who's who in the East
  - Who's who in the western hemisphere
  - Who's who (international)
  - Wickenden, E
  - Wiel, Harry I
  - Wiener, Alexander S
  - Wiesenthal, Alfred
  - Wiggins, James W
  - Wignall, Ernest W
  - Wilberforce, Octavia
  - Wilcox, Maurice J
  - Wilde, Charles E., Jr.
  - Wiley, Alexander
  - Wiley, John, & Sons, Inc.
    - Ancharoff, Maurice
  - Wilford, B S
  - Wilkins, Jim
  - Wilkinson, J T